<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SmartForm</string>
    <string name="title_name">SMARTFORM</string>
    <string name="testBtn_text">TEST</string>
    <string name="resultBtn_text">RESULT</string>
    <string name="uploadBtn_text">UPLOAD</string>
    <string name="aboutBtn_text">ABOUT</string>
    <string name="uploadTitle_text">Upload Results</string>
    <string name="uploadResult1_text">Upload Result 1</string>
    <string name="uploadResult2_text">Upload Result 2</string>
    <string name="uploadResult3_text">Upload Result 3</string>
    <string name="about_text">The project is to design a smart phone app analyzing the indoor air concentration of formaldehyde:
        the users will expose the chemical sensor indoor, then take a picture through SmART-Form app.
        The app will recognize the color identity of chemical sensor and return the result of air concentration of formaldehyde. \n\n Shane</string>
    <string name="result_title_text">Latest Results: 3</string>
    <string name="result_01">Result 1</string>
    <string name="result_02">Result 2</string>
    <string name="result_03">Result 3</string>
    <string name="btn_start_test">Start Test</string>
    <string name="cannot">Cannot</string>
    <string name="album_name">SampleBadge</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hint_image_capture">Enter a title for Picture</string>
    <string name="capture_image">Snap</string>
    <string name="save_camera">Save</string>
    <string name="recapture_image">Retake Picture</string>
    <string name="capturing_image">Image Preview</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="btn_create_test">New Project</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="title_activity_camera">CameraActivity</string>
    <string name="before_bitmapBtn">Before Exposure</string>
    <string name="after_bitmapBtn">After Exposure</string>

    <!-- TODO -->
    <string name="title_activity_test">testActivity</string>
    <string name="test_title_hint">Enter a title for the test.</string>

    <string name="test_title_label">Title</string>
    <string name="test_details_label">Details</string>
    <string name="test_finished_label">finished?</string>
    <string name="tests_title">tests</string>
    <string name="date_picker_title">Date of test</string>
    <string name="time_picker_title">Time of test</string>

    <string name="new_test">New test</string>
    <string name="show_subtitle">Hint</string>
    <string name="hide_subtitle">Hide</string>
    <string name="subtitle">App Hint</string>
    <string name="hints">
        Instructions:

        \n1.You should have a chemical badge along with the app.
        \n2.Open the app and select “New test”, name your test.
        \n3.Select the “Before” button and take a picture of the badge before exposure.
        \n4.Save your test and keep the badge still for 72hrs exposure.
        \n5.Select the “After” button and take a picture of the badge after exposure.
        \n6.Save your test and select “Data Survey”, complete the sampling survey.
        \n7.Complete the follow-up community testing surveys."
    </string>
    <string name="delete_test">Delete</string>

    <string name="no_tests">There are currently no tests to display.</string>
    <string name="add_new_test">New test</string>

    <string name="take">Snap It</string>
    <string name="add_image">Add image</string>
    <string name="image_of_test">Photographic evidence of test</string>

    <string name="test_report_text">Data Survey</string>
    
    <string name="test_report">%1$s:
        The test was created on %2$s. %3$s, and the result is %4$s.</string>
    <string name="test_report_finished">The test is finished</string>
    <string name="test_report_unfinished">The test is not finished</string>
    <string name="test_report_subject">Smartform test Report</string>
    <string name="send_report">Send test report</string>
    <string name="result">Result</string>
    <string name="survey">Survey</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="disagree">Disagree</string>
    <string name="about">ABOUT</string>
    <string name="info">INFO</string>
    <string name="copyright">
        COPYRIGHT:

        \nCopyright 2017 SMARTFORM.

        \nThe Ohio State University.

        \nAll Rights Reserved.

        \n\nSmartPhone App for Residential Testing of Formaldehyde (SmART-Form)

        \nDepartment of Civil, Environmental and Geodetic Engineering</string>
    <string name="eula">
        This is a consent form for your participation in this research study.

        \n\nThe purpose of this research project is to develop a low-cost and highly accurate technique for assessing
        domestic formaldehyde concentrations and is being conducted by Ohio State University in conjunction with the
        Public Laboratory for Open Technology and Science (Public Lab). Insights from citizen scientists and other
        relevant members of the public are key to developing the most robust and useable technology possible.

        \n\nYou are invited to participate in this research project because you are:
        A member of an environmental or citizen science organization (Public Lab, Global Community Monitor, or the
        Sierra Club’s formaldehyde campaign) A resident of Waycross, GA where the technology developed by this project
        will be first deployed.

        \n\nYour participation in this research study is voluntary. You may choose not to participate. If you decide to
        participate in this research survey, you may withdraw at any time. If you decide not to participate in this
        study or if you withdraw from participating at any time, there will be no penalty or loss of benefits that
        the participant is entitled to. You may skip any questions you do not wish to answer. If you want do not wish
        to complete this survey just close your browser.

        \n\nThe procedure involves filling an online survey that will take approximately 20 minutes. Your responses will
        be confidential and we do not collect identifying information such as your name, email address or IP address.
        The survey questions will be about your interest in testing for airborne formaldehyde, how we should build
        the software and hardware for this technology to best suit your needs, and reflections on past community
        science studies (if applicable).

        \n\nWe will work to make sure that no one sees your survey responses without approval. But, because we are using
        the Internet, there is a chance that someone could access your online responses without permission. In some
        cases, this information could be used to identify you. Your data will be protected with a code to reduce the
        risk that other people can view the responses. We will do our best to keep your information confidential.
        All data is stored in a password protected electronic format. To help protect your confidentiality, the surveys
        will not contain information that will personally identify you. The results of this study will be used for
        scholarly, technical development, public education purposes only and may be shared with Ohio State University
        representatives.

        \n\nFor questions, concerns, or complaints about the study, or you feel you have been harmed as a result of study
        participation, you may contact Karen Dannemiller at 614-292-4031.

        \n\nFor questions about your rights as a participant in this study or to discuss other study-related concerns or
        complaints with someone who is not part of the research team, you may contact Ms. Sandra Meadows in the Office
        of Responsible Research Practices at 1-800-678-6251.This research has been reviewed according to Ohio State
        University IRB procedures for research involving human subjects.

        \n\nPlease print a copy of this consent form for your records, if you so desire.


        \n\nELECTRONIC CONSENT: Please select your choice below.

        \n\nClicking on the "agree" button below indicates that:

        \n*You have ready the above information

        \n*You voluntarily agree to participate

        \n*You are at least 18 years of age

        \n\nIf you do not wish to participate in the research study,
        please decline participation by clicking on the "disagree" button.
    </string>

    <string name="survey_intro">
        This is an user experience survey.

        \n\n You will be asked for few questions about this app.

        \n\n Please share your comments or suggestions with us.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_intro">IntroActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="error_prompt">Error</string>
    <string name="thanks_prompt">Thanks</string>
    <string name="promoter_prompt">Promoter</string>
    <string name="detractor_prompt">detractor</string>
    <string name="new_survey">Start your survey</string>
    <string name="timer_stop_button">Stop</string>
    <string name="timer_start_button">Start</string>
    <string name="hint">Hints</string>
    <string name="camera_hints">Please match the highlighted triangle with the colored area approximately</string>
    <string name="test_about_text">About Formaldehyde</string>
    <string name="health_survey">Health Survey</string>
    <string name="user_survey">User Survey</string>
    <string name="about_us">
        ABOUT US

        \n\n The purpose of this research project is to design a smartphone app to allow community scientists
        to determine the formaldehyde concentrations in their homes or in outdoor air.

        \n\n We would like to receive feedback from you about your experience using the app.
        Your participation is voluntary and all questions are voluntary.

        \n\n Contributing your data will help us!

        \n\n Email: dannemiller.70@osu.edu

        \n\n Phone: 504-233-0539

        \n\n Website: u.osu.edu/smartform
    </string>
    <string name="TestList">TestList</string>
    <string name="about_title">What does my formaldehyde level mean?</string>
    <string name="about_detail">The exact healthy levels for indoor formaldehyde isn’t set. <b>Here are some current recommendations:</b>
        \n\n• 8 ppb for indoor at home
        \n(Agency for Toxic Substances and Disease Registry (ATSDR) chronic minimum risk level)
        \n• 40 ppb for indoor at home over 8 hours
        \n(Health Canada\'s Residential Indoor Air Quality Guideline for 8 hours)
        \n• 16 ppb for workplace over 8 hours
        \n(NIOSH Recommended Exposure Limit (REL) for 8 hours)
        \n• 750 ppb (500 ppb action level) for workplace danger limit:   \t(OSHA workplace limit)
        \n\n<b>Here are two ways to cut down indoor formaldehyde levels:</b>
        \n\n<b>STEP 1 Remove or stop the source. Common sources include:</b>
        \n• Smoking
        \n• Pressed wood products (plywood/particleboard)
        \n• Adhesives used in new carpet
        \n• Certain types of new hardwood flooring
        \n• Gas stove
        \n• Other gas appliances
        \n• Use of nail polish
        \n• Use of adhesives/glues
        \n• Use of paints
        \n• New indoor paint
        \n• All-purpose cleaner (certain types)
        \n• Window cleaner (certain types)
        \n\n<b>Other steps might include:</b>
        \n\n• Not smoking indoors
        \n• Removing pressed wood products (plywood/particleboard)
        \n• When possible, go outdoors if you must use paints/adhesives/glues\nail polish
        \n• Using a vent fan with gas appliances
        \n• Using no-VOC or low-VOC indoor paint
        \n• Changing to natural cleaning products or soap and water
        \n\n<b>STEP 2: Increase ventilation.</b>
        \n\nThis only applies if the outdoor air has low formaldehyde concentrations, which it does in most cases.
        \n• Open windows (this works best by opening windows on two sides of the house for a cross-breeze)
        \n• Window fans (drawing outdoor air into the house)
        \n\n<b>Other steps might include:</b>
        \n\n• Home air filters and purifiers - Activated carbon filters are the best for removing formaldehyde,
        but they may not work for long because they get saturated quickly. Otherwise, home air filters and
        purifiers don’t usually work well on changing indoor formaldehyde levels. Household plants can also
        improve overall indoor air quality, but their ability to reduce formaldehyde is likely very small.
        \n\n<b>Indoor Formaldehyde and Health</b>
        \n\nFormaldehyde can cause irritation to the skin and lining of the eyes,
        nose, mouth, throat, and airways. This irritation might worsen the symptoms for people with conditions like
        respiratory diseases and allergies. Being around higher levels of formaldehyde for long periods of time has
        also been linked to some cancers.
        \n\n<i>More information can be found at www.epa.gov/formaldehyde</i>
        \n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="cancel_camera">Cancel</string>
    <string name="contributors">

        \nOhio State Team:
        \nKaren C. Dannemiller
        \nSiyang Zhang
        \nRongjun Qin
        \nSarah Haines
        \nDavid Kormos
        \nPaige Frey
        \n
        \nPublic Lab Team:
        \nNicholas Shapiro
        \nGretchen Gehrke
        \n
        \nConsultant:
        \nJessica Castner
        \n
        \nSyracuse Team:
        \nZhenlei Liu
        \nBeverly Guo
        \nJianshun Zhang
        \n
        \nCommunity Member:
        \nJoan Tibor
        \n
        \nIndustry Partner:
        \nMorphix Technologies
        \n
        \nFunding: National Science Foundation
        \n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
    </string>

    <string-array name="temp_array">
        <item>&lt;65°F</item>
        <item>65-80°F</item>
        <item>&gt;80°F</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="humd_array">
        <item>0-80% RH</item>
        <item>>80% RH</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
